
> test
> node --test --test-concurrency=1 workspace.test.mjs

✔ React shell has local assets, accessible navigation, no personal startup reads or microphone (3922.9802ms)
✔ typed note preserves whitespace, Unicode and raw/formatted pairing, without capture-time invention (1455.486ms)
✔ a committed typed-note response lost in transit can be retried without duplicate observation (988.8904ms)
✔ imports and reimports exact paired evidence through isolated PostgreSQL (1440.597ms)
✔ invalid and conflicting imports fail atomically without echoing driver/input errors (1032.5746ms)
✔ source markup remains literal text with no executable element or outside request (1027.7951ms)
✔ large file is rejected before reads; pagination reaches every original (1420.4198ms)
✔ search keeps conflicting variants and distinguishes undated, absent evidence and outage (1942.9775ms)
✔ learned memories retain conditional meaning, unknown times and superseded history (6886.39ms)
✔ Ask cites original evidence, diagnoses feedback and permits only one explicit retry (3118.0603ms)
✔ Ask failure is not an unknown answer, and retry is explicit (654.3606ms)
✔ Private unmounts all content, file state and scratchpad without reads or backfill (1206.5886ms)
✔ Private cancels pending source, ignores the late result and prevents follow-up reads (1072.7051ms)
✔ Private cancels pending search, ignores the late result and prevents follow-up reads (1111.1713ms)
✔ Private cancels pending memory, ignores the late result and prevents follow-up reads (1324.7441ms)
✔ Private cancels pending ask, ignores the late result and prevents follow-up reads (1719.6324ms)
✔ Private cancels pending usage, ignores the late result and prevents follow-up reads (1258.1404ms)
✔ unknown backend errors stay bounded; loading a collection is not mistaken for empty on failure (728.3267ms)
✔ sample import is idempotent; usage reports measured payloads, timings and unknown billing (1720.7178ms)
✔ mobile keyboard, dialog focus and back navigation do not restore personal text (1490.1201ms)
✔ Private scratchpad is cleared before browser-history restoration (748.4245ms)
✔ greeting explains capabilities locally and evidence choices are explained and collapsed (679.3587ms)
✔ 540-note import, setup information and 30 preselected showcase questions use real APIs (2394.0971ms)
✔ mobile Correct, world change and Forget review effects and clear revoked cached results (9263.0122ms)
ℹ tests 24
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 24
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 51958.8205
